WASEEM KASHIF

Frontend Developer | Mentor | Team Leader

노 +974-3007-8398 🛾 @ waseemqulandar@gmail.com 📝 https://profile-portfolio-nine.vercel.app/



STRENGTHS



Coding Expert

Proficient in Next.js, Tailwind, JavaScript



Problem Solver

Innovative approach to challenges



Team Player

Excellent collaboration skills

SKILLS

CSS HTML JavaScript Rest API's Next.js

TypeScript GIT React.is

Vue.js SvelteKit Redux

Material UI Tailwind CSS

Magento

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Igra University

Pre-Engineering HSSC II

Aga Khan Heigher Secondary School.

2014 - 2016

♥ Karimabad FB Area, Karachi, PK

Matric (science)

The Aga Khan School

= 2011 - 2014

♥ Kharadar, Karachi, PK

SUMMARY

Passionate Frontend Developer with a knack for creating intuitive and highperforming web applications.

I excel at motivating, mentoring & developing teams of less experienced developers. I have 5+ years of experience and ambitious web design professional seeking an opportunity as a front-end developer. Detail-oriented professional with an associate degree in computer science and proven experience with a web development firm and Ecommerce Group.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Frontend Developer

Ansar Gallery, A&H MARKET

Senior front-end web developer for ahmarket.com.

- · I was hired to develop the ahmarket website, a leading e-commerce platform in the GCC.
- This website is currently on the Magento CMS platform.

Frontend Developer

Uconnect Technologies

ii 02/2024 - 2024 **♀** Gilgit, PK

Worked on various web development projects

- · Contributed to the development of 10+ websites
- · Responsible for converting figma designs into real time responsive web applications using required technologies.

Junior Frontend Developer

Uconnect Technologies

= 2020 - 2021 Gilgit, PK

Assisted in the development of web applications

- · Worked on multiple small web development projects
- · Improved web skills by learings and working on real time projects.
- · Received 'Rising Star' award for outstanding performance.

INDUSTRY EXPERTISE

Front-end develoment Backend, DevOps

LANGUAGES

Proficient English + Urdu

> Powered by CY Enhancy